[
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c40",
      "correctAnswer": "The Red Baron",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Blue Baron",
        "The Yellow Baron",
        "The Black Baron"
      ],
      "question": "By what name was Baron Manfred von Richthofen better known?",
      "tags": [
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c27",
      "correctAnswer": "Henry VIII",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Charles I",
        "William the Conqueror",
        "James III"
      ],
      "question": "Who was the father of Queen Elizabeth I of England?",
      "tags": [
        "kings",
        "uk",
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c08",
      "correctAnswer": "Richard Nixon",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Donald Trump",
        "Ronald Reagan",
        "George W Bush"
      ],
      "question": "Which President of the USA infamously allowed the bugging of the Democratic Committee headquarters?",
      "tags": [
        "presidents",
        "events",
        "usa",
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a1a",
      "correctAnswer": "Marie Antoinette",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Eleanor of Aquitaine",
        "Margaret of Provence",
        "Maria Theresa"
      ],
      "question": "Which Queen of France was beheaded in 1793?",
      "tags": [
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f95189b",
      "correctAnswer": "Italian",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Spanish",
        "French",
        "English"
      ],
      "question": "What was the nationality of Marco Polo?",
      "tags": [
        "exploration",
        "people",
        "middle_ages",
        "medieval",
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a6c",
      "correctAnswer": "Pirate",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Judge",
        "Prime Minister",
        "General"
      ],
      "question": " What was Sir Henry Morgan famous for in the 17th century?",
      "tags": [
        "people",
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a1b",
      "correctAnswer": "Pearl Harbour",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "D Day",
        "The bombing of hiroshima",
        "The Nazi invasion of France"
      ],
      "question": "Which military attack took place on Dec. 7, 1941?",
      "tags": [
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "62611f444b176d54800e3d4d",
      "correctAnswer": "1962",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "1950",
        "1970",
        "1973"
      ],
      "question": "When did the Cuban Missile Crisis bring the world to the brink of nuclear war?",
      "tags": [
        "events",
        "politics",
        "cold_war",
        "usa",
        "russia",
        "cuba",
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9ec",
      "correctAnswer": "John Adams",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Herbert Hoover",
        "Calvin Coolidge",
        "Ulysses S. Grant"
      ],
      "question": "Who was the 2nd president of the USA, in term during the period 1797â€“1801?",
      "tags": [
        "presidents",
        "usa",
        "history"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "id": "639898395c9a75021f310465",
      "correctAnswer": "1939",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "1941",
        "1945",
        "1937"
      ],
      "question": "What year did World War II begin?",
      "tags": [
        "history",
        "world_war_2",
        "wars"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    }
  ]